adayinmotherhood.com 2014-12-08

# Privacy Policy/ Disclaimer - A Day in Motherhood

**4** Flares Twitter 1 Facebook 2 Google+ 1 Email \-- StumbleUpon 0 LinkedIn 0 Reddit 0 Filament.io **4** Flares ×

A Day in Motherhood prohibits the use of their website and/or services in any manner associated with the transmission, distribution or delivery of any unsolicited bulk or unsolicited commercial e-mail ("Spam"). You may not use any A Day in Motherhood services to send Spam. You also may not deliver Spam or cause Spam to be delivered to any customers of A Day in Motherhood.

In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (15 U.S.C. 7701, et seq., Public Law No. 108-187, was S.877 of the 108th United States Congress), e-mail sent, or caused to be sent, to or through the A Day in Motherhood webiste or service may not:

  * use or contain invalid or forged headers;
  * use or contain invalid or non-existent domain names;
  * employ any technique to otherwise misrepresent, hide or obscure any information in identifying the point of origin or the transmission path;
  * use other means of deceptive addressing;
  * use a third party's internet domain name, or be relayed from or through a third party's equipment, without permission of the third party;
  * contain false or misleading information in the subject line or otherwise contain false or misleading content;
  * fail to comply with additional technical standards described below;
  * otherwise violate our Terms of Use.

A Day in Motherhood does not authorize the harvesting, mining or collection of e-mail addresses or other information from or through the website or its services. A Day in Motherhood does not permit or authorize others to use the A Day in Motherhood services to collect, compile or obtain any information about its customers or subscribers, including but not limited to subscriber e-mail addresses. 

A Day in Motherhood does not permit or authorize any attempt to use its services in a manner that could damage, disable, overburden or impair any aspect of any of the services, or that could interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of any A Day in Motherhood service.

If A Day in Motherhood believes that unauthorized or improper use is being made of any service, it may, without notice, take such action as it, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate, including blocking messages from a particular internet domain, mail server or IP address. A Day in Motherhood may immediately terminate any account on any service which it determines, in its sole discretion, is transmitting or is otherwise connected with any e-mail that violates this policy.

Nothing in this policy is intended to grant any right to transmit or send e-mail to, or through, the A Day in Motherhood website and/or services. Failure to enforce this policy in every instance does not amount to a waiver of A Day in Motherhood's rights.

Unauthorized use of any A Day in Motherhood services in connection with the transmission of unsolicited e-mail, including the transmission of e-mail in violation of this policy, may result in civil, criminal, or administrative penalties against the sender and those assisting the sender. 

Violators of the CAN SPAM Act may be subject to “cease and desist” orders or penalties from the FTC (Federal Trade Commission) of up to $11,000 per violation. Criminal prosecution is also possible in the case of egregious offenders, which can result in penalties such as fines, forfeiture of proceeds and equipment. The worst offenders can also be subject to prison time.

A Day in Motherhood  
www.adayinmotherhood.com

lomargie@rfehosting.com

**Giveaway/ Review Disclaimer**

_**ADayinMotherhood.com is the writer and distributor of  posts, reviews, giveaways, deals and any other material presented {unless otherwise indicated}.  100% of the opinions and writings are ADayinMotherhood.com’s and can not be duplicated without prior permission.  Images and links were used with permission from the website/ promoters discussed. **_

_**ADayinMotherhood.com is not responsible for the delivery of the winners prizes.  All complaints  and dissatisfactions with the website or products within are to be discussed with the sponsoring company. **_

_**Giveaway winners are chosen by a random generator and failure to follow the rules of entry disqualifies that entry.**_ _ **By entering this giveaway, you understand and agree thatADayinMotherhood.com is is no way responsible for the production, delivery, or quality of the received product.**_

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use of personal information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy.

When accessing our Website, A Day in Motherhood will learn certain information about you during your visit.

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site, your IP address.

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.  
**IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.  
**Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone.  
**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other items and services to our customers and prospective customers.

A Day in Motherhood will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

**  
A Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our web site and services and we ask that minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.  
**How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information is never transmitted via email.

A Day in Motherhood may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, A Day in Motherhood uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.  
**Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**  
Contact**

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or your dealings with our web site, please contact us.

A Day in Motherhood  
www.adayinmotherhood.com

lomargie@rfehosting.com

**Links Disclaimer**

The A Day in Motherhood web site may contain links to many other web sites. A Day in Motherhood cannot guarantee the accuracy of information found at any linked site. Links to or from external web sites sites not owned or controlled by A Day in Motherhood does not constitute an endorsement by A Day in Motherhood or any of its employees of the sponsors of these sites or the products or information presented there.

**4** Flares Twitter 1 Facebook 2 Google+ 1 Email \-- StumbleUpon 0 LinkedIn 0 Reddit 0 Filament.io **4** Flares ×
